

Profile

Full-stack web developer leveraging a background in marketing to help maximize the user experience for all users on the web. Earned a certificate in full-stack web development from Rutgers, State University of New Jersey Coding Boot camp. Known among staff & classmates for strong attention to detail, creativity, & ready to tackle any project or assignment no matter the complexity.

Employment History

Senior Account Manager, Choice Bank, Golden Valley, MN

JANUARY 2019 - AUGUST 2020

- Actively developing new business & expanding existing customer relationship through networking, tabling events, & visiting local businesses.
- Review products & services of existing clients to ensure they utilize all their services to help them maximize growth & success to their full potential.

Account Manager II, Venture/Choice Bank, Golden Valley, MN

FEBRUARY 2017 - JANUARY 2019

- Managing new/existing book of business by conducting regular customer reviews to ensure my clients have all the products and services needed to maximize growth.
- Creating brand awareness in the community by attending local network events
- Utilize social network to spread the word on local network events or seminars held at our offices.

Account Executive, Venture Bank, Golden Valley, MN

AUGUST 2015 - FEBRUARY 2017

- Providing exceptional service by working closely with bank officers to strengthen and expand core customer relationships while resolving client issues that arise to improve their business workflow & add efficiency.
- Promote deposit products & services to new/existing clients in order to help grow their business & ensure their financial business needs are met.
- Administer all deposit products & services using integrated banking programs, platforms, and software systems.

Sr. Customer Service Representative, Venture Bank, Bloomington, MN

FEBRUARY 2015 - AUGUST 2015

- Respond promptly to our clients immediate needs related to transaction processing, online banking access & deposit account functionality & records.
- Use generalist knowledge to interact with and make appropriate referrals to both internal & external customers.
- Review all new accounts established to ensure they have been setup properly and all required documentation has been obtained.

Staffing Manager, Robert Half International - Accountemps, Bloomington, MN

FEBRUARY 2014 - SEPTEMBER 2014

Details

Excelsior MN, 55331 (763) 381-1383 <u>vladimir.s.dimitrov14@gmail.com</u>

Links

www.linkedin.com/in/vladimirsdimitrov https://github.com/Vlady14 https://vdimitrov-portfolio.herokuapp.com

Skills

Marketing
Customer Service
Microsoft Office
Microsoft Excel
Microsoft PowerPoint
B2B Sales
Marketing and Sales
Interpersonal Communication Skills
Leadership and Teamwork
Social Networking
Event Planning
JavaScript
jQuery
HTML & CSS
React.js
JSON
AJAX
Node.js

Personal & Small Business Banker II, Wells Fargo Bank, N.A., Eden Prairie, MN

JANUARY 2013 - FEBRUARY 2014

Personal Banker I, Wells Fargo Bank, N.A., Eden Prairie, MN

FEBRUARY 2011 - JANUARY 2013

Education

Coding Bootcamp Certificate, Rutgers State University, Camden, NJ

OCTOBER 2020 - JANUARY 2021

12-week intensive program focused on gaining technical programming skills in HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, JQuery, Bootstrap, API's, Node Js, MySQL, MongoDB Atlas, Express, & ReactJS

Bachelors Degree in Marketing, Metropolitan State University, Saint Paul, MN

AUGUST 2014 - DECEMBER 2016

General Education, Normandale Community College, Bloomington, MN

AUGUST 2008 - MAY 2014

MySQL

MongoDB